Compiled from "TerminalViewClient.java"
public interface com.termux.view.TerminalViewClient {
  public abstract float onScale(float);
  public abstract void onSingleTapUp(android.view.MotionEvent);
  public abstract boolean shouldBackButtonBeMappedToEscape();
  public abstract boolean shouldEnforceCharBasedInput();
  public abstract boolean shouldUseCtrlSpaceWorkaround();
  public abstract boolean isTerminalViewSelected();
  public abstract void copyModeChanged(boolean);
  public abstract boolean onKeyDown(int, android.view.KeyEvent, com.termux.terminal.TerminalSession);
  public abstract boolean onKeyUp(int, android.view.KeyEvent);
  public abstract boolean onLongPress(android.view.MotionEvent);
  public abstract boolean readControlKey();
  public abstract boolean readAltKey();
  public abstract boolean readShiftKey();
  public abstract boolean readFnKey();
  public abstract boolean onCodePoint(int, boolean, com.termux.terminal.TerminalSession);
  public abstract void onEmulatorSet();
  public abstract void logError(java.lang.String, java.lang.String);
  public abstract void logWarn(java.lang.String, java.lang.String);
  public abstract void logInfo(java.lang.String, java.lang.String);
  public abstract void logDebug(java.lang.String, java.lang.String);
  public abstract void logVerbose(java.lang.String, java.lang.String);
  public abstract void logStackTraceWithMessage(java.lang.String, java.lang.String, java.lang.Exception);
  public abstract void logStackTrace(java.lang.String, java.lang.Exception);
}
